A Guide to the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease records FA057
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Reports, 1910-1914; 5; 5 Bound Volumes
  Annual Reports can also be found in Series 3: Minutes and Reports.
  Annual reports
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Report 1910 (Item REF 616.965 4 ROC 1910)
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Report 1911 (Item REF 616.965 4 ROC 1911)
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Report 1912 (Item REF 616.965 4 ROC 1912)
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Report 1913 (Item REF 616.965 4 ROC 1913)
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission Annual Report 1914 (Item REF 616.965 4 ROC 1914)